Before we get into specific case studies,
在学习具体的案例研究之前
I want to talk a bit about how to approach solving tasks with machine learning.
我先介绍下如何使用机器学习完成任务
Generally, the algorithms you use can be broken
通常 算法可以分成两大类
down into two major types; supervised, and unsupervised.
分别是监督式和非监督式算法
I find it helpful to think of these in the context
举个例子比较好理解
of a specific example, image classification.
例如图像分类
Say we've been given a bunch of images of vehicle types.
假设有大量车辆图像
Supervised learning means that our training data is
监督式学习是指训练数据
made of images and their corresponding class labels.
由图像及其对应的类别标签组成
So we'll have images of cars, bikes,
这些图像包括汽车 自行车
buses, and so on,
巴士等等
all with their true label.
都带有真实标签
The label is also called the ground truth.
标签也称为参考标准
Then we can train an image classifier that takes in an image as input.
然后用输入图像训练图像分类器
Its goal is to produce a label that is as close to the true class label as possible.
目标是生成尽量接近真实类别标签的标签
As we train the classifier,
当我们训练分类器时
it tries to improve its accuracy.
它会尝试提高准确率
Supervised learning basically means we have a certain known target,
监督式学习是指在训练过程中
in this case, the known label,
我们有已知目标
to aim for during the training process.
即已知标签
We achieve a successful training when the model is highly
当模型能够非常准确地学习
accurate at learning how to predict true labels,
如何预测从未见过的数据的真实标签时
given new data it hasn't seen before.
模型就训练成功了
In other words, data that wasn't part of a training set.
也就是不属于训练集的数据
Now, let's think about how we might approach this task if we were not given any labels.
下面思考下 如果没有给定任何标签 该如何处理这个任务
So our training set is made of unlabeled images.
训练集由无标签图像组成
We'll have to take an unsupervised approach.
我们需要采用非监督式方法
This means that instead of relying on
所以我们无法依赖于
given information about how to group all labeled data,
如何分组所有带标签数据的已知信息
we have to rely on finding natural groupings in the data.
只能依赖于查找数据中的自然分组规律
We can train an algorithm to separate images into clusters
我们可以训练算法根据感知的
according to perceived similarities in color or geometric traits.
颜色或几何特性相似性将图像分隔成聚类
But we don't really have a way of checking that these groupings are correct or incorrect.
但是我们无法检查这些分组是否正确
So there is no measure for accuracy.
所以无法衡量准确率
We'll have to develop a new metric for separating data into groups.
我们需要开发对数据分组的新指标
Something like the distance between similar and different groups of data,
例如相似和不同数据分组之间的距离
and at the end of a training,
在训练结束时
will end up with an image clustering algorithm.
将获得一个图像聚类算法
The way images are clustered together is really meant to give us some insight
图像聚类到一起可以告诉我们
into what patterns naturally emerge from a given dataset.
给定数据集存在哪些自然模式
In this first lesson,
在第一节课
you'll focus on finding patterns in data using
你将学习使用 Amazon Sagemaker 中的
a variety of unsupervised algorithms in Amazon Sagemaker.
各种非监督式算法查找数据中的规律
By the end of this lesson,
学完这节课后
you should be able to utilize Sagemaker resources,
你将能够利用 Sagemaker 资源
and apply these techniques to task of your own design.
将这些技巧运用到你自己设计的任务上